<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference on HeSteIT</title>
    <link>https://hesteit.github.io/categories/conference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conference on HeSteIT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hesteit.github.io/categories/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Networking Day Recap</title>
      <link>https://hesteit.github.io/posts/networking-day-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hesteit.github.io/posts/networking-day-recap/</guid>
      <description>On tuesday, I was one of 250 attendees of the first virtual „European Networking Day&amp;quot;. This event was brought to life by the organizers of the European Cloud Conference and European Collaboration Summit. I spent almost 5 hours in virtual reality (the event was organized using AltspaceVR) and really had a great time, so I thought it would be nice to do a quick recap for everyone that couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend or for others planning to do such events in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time @Microsoft Ignite – Lessons learned</title>
      <link>https://hesteit.github.io/posts/first-time-at-microsoft-ignite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hesteit.github.io/posts/first-time-at-microsoft-ignite/</guid>
      <description>This year, I attended my very first Microsoft Ignite in Orlando, Florida. Besides some very interesting announcements (I’ll cover the most important ones from my point of view in the second part), I thought it would be nice to share some advice for other &amp;ldquo;newcomers&amp;rdquo; when they go for their first Microsoft Ignite…
Plan your schedule ahead! Plan your schedule weeks in advance. I didn’t plan my sessions until each morning, which led to nervous looking-at-my-phone-while-walking in the morning and searching-for-the-next-session while sitting in another session – both of which is quite distracting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
